ENGLISH TEACHER RESUME

Personal Details

Name: Heather Bell

Date of Birth: 14/09/1998Address: Florida City, USA

• Phone: (578)736 7827

• Email: Bell14Heather@gmail.com

Summary

Heather Bell is an experienced English Teacher with a passion for helping students understand and apply Logical concepts. She has a proven track record of designing and delivering creative and effective lesson plans that engage students and ensure success. He possesses excellent communication and interpersonal skills and is an enthusiastic team player.

Work Experience

- English Teacher, Florida Preparatory High School, Florida 2022- 2024 – Present
 - Designing and delivering effective lesson plans for students of all levels.
 - Monitoring student performance and providing feedback.
 - Working with other teachers to develop new teaching methods.
- English Tutor, Broward County Public School, Florida City -2020 – 2022
 - Providing individual and small group tutoring for English students.
 - Developing lesson plans to help students improve their understanding of English concepts.
 - Assisting students with English homework.

Education

- Bachelor of Education in English Literature Georgetown University, USA – 2015 - 2018
- Master of Arts in English Language and Literature Florida International University, USA -2018 - 2020

Skills

- Excellent communication and interpersonal skills.
- · Strong problem-solving skills.
- · Attention to detail and proofreading expertise.
- · Proficient in AP style and grammar rules.

Achievements

100% result throughout the teaching career.

Students enjoy learning with me.